<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cole Peterson&#39;s Sports Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cole Peterson&#39;s Sports Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How the Cubs broke the 108-year drought in 2016</title>
      <link>/2022/04/21/how-the-cubs-broke-the-108-year-drought-in-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/21/how-the-cubs-broke-the-108-year-drought-in-2016/</guid>
      <description>108 years.
That’s how long it had been since the Chicago Cubs won their last MLB World Series trophy. After over a century, the “Lovable losers” knocked off the then Cleveland Indians to take the series 4-3 and hoist the ultimate prize.
But how did they do it?
Sure they had the NL MVP and Cy Young in Kris Bryant and Jake Arrieta. But baseball is a team sport, so let’s take a deeper dive into the Cubs championship run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Has Nikola Jokic done enough to earn back-to-back NBA MVP awards?</title>
      <link>/2022/04/07/has-nikola-jokic-done-enough-to-earn-back-to-back-nba-mvp-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/07/has-nikola-jokic-done-enough-to-earn-back-to-back-nba-mvp-awards/</guid>
      <description>The MVP race in the NBA is the closest it’s ever been. In recent weeks it has ultimately been narrowed down to three very polarizing candidates.
Giannis Antetokounmpo, Joel Embiid and Nikola Jokic.
Four players have been repeat winners of the NBA’s most prestige award over the last 13 years. The Joker looks to be the fifth, and perhaps the most impressive player analytically in recent memory.
Lets take a look at how he’s getting it done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Cole Peterson</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Cole Peterson is a current sophomore at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln with a major in sports media and communications and a minor in business. He works in the athletic department as a student communications assistant and will be interning with USA Baseball over the summer. He hopes to obtain a job in media relations after college in either professional or collegiate sports. Cole is originally from Elkhorn, Neb., and has lived in Nebraska all 20 years of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
